Guide to the Samuel Stark Film stills: photographs, 1925-1972
Department of Special Collections
- 732. "Promise Her Anything", 3 (Box 9)
  Warren Beatty, Leslie Caron
- 733. "This Property Is Condemned" (Box 9)
  Natalie Wood, Robert Redford
- 734. "Prudence and the Pill" (Box 9)
  Deborah Kerr, David Niven
- 735. "Public Enemy", 2 (Box 9)
- 736. "Puddin'Head" (Box 9)
  Judy Canova, Francis Lederer
- 737. "The Pumpkin Eater", 3 (Box 9)
  Anne Bancroft, Peter Finch
- 738. "The Purple Plain", 3 (Box 9)
  Gregory Peck
- 739. "Pursuit of Happiness"1934 (Box 9)
  Francis Lederer, Joan Bennett
- 740. "Pygmalion" (Box 9)
  Leslie Howard, Wendy Hiller
- 741. "Quartermass and the Pit" (Box 9)
  James Donald, Barbara Shelley
- 742. "Quartermass Xperiment", 2 (Box 9)
  Brian Donlevy, Jack Warner
- 743. "Queen of Sheba"1921 (Box 9)
- 744. "The Raging Tide"1951 (Box 10)
  Richard Conte, Alex Nicol
- 745. "Rain" (Box 10)
  Joan Crawford
- 746. "Ramona"1936, 3 (Box 10)
  Loretta Young, Don Ameche
- 747. "Rasputin"1932, 2 (Box 10)
  Lionel, Ethel, and John Barrymore
- 748. "The Raven" (Box 10)
  Vincent Price, Peter Lorre, Boris Karloff
- 749. "Reap the Wild Wind"1941 (Box 10)
  Ray Milland, John Wayne, Paulette
- 750. "Rebecca", 2 (Box 10)
  Laurence Olivier, Joan Fontaine
- 751. "Rebecca of Sunnybrook Farm"1924 (Box 10)
- 752. "Red Ball Express"1952 (Box 10)
  Jeff Chandler, Alex Nichol
- 753. "The Red Dancer"1928, 2 (Box 10)
- 754. "Red Dust" (Box 10)
  Clark Gable, Mary Astor
- 755. "Red Garters" (Box 10)
  Rosemary Clooney, Jack Carson
- 756. "The Red Inn" (Box 10)
  Fernandel, Francoise Rosay
- 757. "The Red Pony" (Box 10)
  (see Steinbeck Collection)
- 758. "Redemption"1929 (Box 10)
- 759. "The Reluctant Dragon"1939 (Box 10)
- 760. "Resurrection"1931 (Box 10)
  Lupe Velez
- 761. "Revenge"1928 (Box 10)
- 762. "Rhythm of the Islands"1943 (Box 10)
- 763. "Rich Man's Folly"1931 (Box 10)
  George Bancroft, Juliette Compton
- 764. "Ricochet Romance" (Box 10)
  Rudy Vallee, Benay Venuta
- 765. "Ride the Pink Horse"1947 (Box 10)
  Robert Montgomery, Thomas Gomez, Wanda Hendrix
- 766. "Rigoletto", 4 (Box 10)
  Tito Gobbi, Lina Pagliughi
- 767. "Ring of Spies", 7 (Box 10)
  Bernard Lee, William Sylvester
- 768. "The River"1929 (Box 10)
  Charles Farrell, Mary Duncan
- 769. "Robin Hood" (Box 10)
  Douglas Fairbanks
- 770. "Rock, Pretty Baby!" (Box 10)
  Sal Mineo, Luanna Patten
- 771. "Rockets Galore" (Box 10)
  Jeannie Carson, Donald Sinden
- 772. "Rocky Mountain", 2 (Box 10)
  Errol Flynn
- 773. "Roman Scandals"1934 (Box 10)
  Eddie Cantor
- 774. "A Romance of the Redwoods"1917 (Box 10)
  Hobart Bosworth, Mary
- 775. "Romanoff and Juliet" (Box 10)
  Peter Ustinov, Sandra Dee
- 776. "Romeo and Juliet"1968 (Box 10)
  Olivia Hussey, Leonard Whiting (6,
- 777. "The Rook", 2 (Box 10)
  Michael York, Heidelinde Weis, Jane Carr
- 778. "The Rosary"1922 (Box 10)
  Robert Gordon, Jane Novak
- 779. "Rose Marie" (Box 10)
  Ann Blyth, Howard Keel, Fernando Lamas
- 780. "Rose of the Rancho"1935 (Box 10)
  John Boles, Gladys Swarthout
- 781. "Rough House Rosie"1927, 2 (Box 10)
- 782. "The Rounder"1929 (Box 10)
  Jack Benny, Polly Moran
- 783. "The Royal Family"1930 (Box 10)
  Ina Claire, Fredric March, Mary Brian
- 784. "Ruggles of Red Gap"1934 (Box 10)
  Charles Laughton, Mary Boland
- 785. "Russia Today"1957, 10 (Box 10)
  documentary
- 786. "Ryan's Daughter" (Box 10)
  John Mills, Robert Mitchum, Trevor Howard, Sarah Miles
- 787. "Sadie Thompson" (Box 10)
  Gloria Swanson, Raoul Walsh
- 788. "The St. Valentine's Day Massacre" (Box 10)
  Jason Robards, George Segal
- 789. "Salome" (Box 10)
  William Fox, Theda Bara
- 790. "The Sand Pebbles"1967 (Box 10)
  Steve McQueen, Richard Attenborough, Candice Bergen
- 791. "The Sandwich Man" (Box 10)
  Michael Bentine, John Le Mesurier
- 792. "The Satan Bug", 2 (Box 10)
  George Maharis, Richard Basehart
- 793. "Saturday Night Out", 2 (Box 10)
  Heather Sears, Bernard Lee
- 794. "Say It With Flowers", 2 (Box 10)
  Mary Clare, Ben Field
- 795. "Scandal At Scourie", 2 (Box 10)
  Greer Garson, Walter Pidgeon
- 796. "Scaramouche", 8 (Box 10)
  Alice Terry, Ramon Navarro
- 797. "Scarface", 3 (Box 10)
- 798. "The Scarlet Empress", 2 (Box 10)
  Marlene Dietrich
- 799. "Scarlet Hours" (Box 10)
  Alison Skipworth, Nancy Carroll
- 800. "The Scarlet Lily"1923 (Box 10)
  Katharine MacDonald
- 801. "The Scoundrel"1935, 6 (Box 10)
  Noel Coward, Julie Haydon
- 802. "Sea Beast" (Box 10)
- 803. "The Sea Hawk"1924, 6 (Box 10)
  Milton Sills, Enid Bennett
- 804. "The Sea Wolf"1920 (Box 10)
  Mabel Scott, Raymond Hatton, Noah Beery
- 805. "Seconds"1966, 2 (Box 10)
  Rock Hudson, Salome Jens
- 806. "Secret Fury", 2 (Box 10)
  Claudette Colbert, Robert Ryan
- 807. "The Secret of Mme Blauche" (Box 10)
- 808. "The Secret of My Success" (Box 10)
  Shirley Jones, Stella
- 809. "Secret of the Incas" (Box 10)
  Charlton Heston, Robert Young
- 810. "Seduced and Abandoned" (Box 10)
  Oreste Palelia, Stefania
- 811. "See You In Hell, Darling" (Box 10)
  Stuart Whitman, Janet Leigh
- 812. "Seminole Uprising" (Box 10)
  George Montgomery
- 813. "Send Me No Flowers" (Box 10)
- 814. "Seven Bad Men"1954, 2 (Box 10)
  Randolph Scott, Forrest Tucker
- 815. "Seven Deadly Sins" (Box 10)
  Michele Morgan, Henry Vidal
- 816. "Seven Keys" (Box 10)
  Jeannie Carson, Alan Dobie, Delphi
- 817. "Seventh Commandment"1957 (Box 10)
  Edwige Feuillere
- 818. "The Seventh Dawn" (Box 10)
  William Holden, Susannah York
- 819. "Seventh Heaven" 1937 (Box 10)
  James Stewart
- 820. "Shadow of a Doubt" (Box 10)
  Theresa Wright, Joseph Cotton
- 821. "Shadowed" (Box 10)
  Anita Louise, Lloyd Corrigan
- 822. "Shake Hands With The Devil" (Box 10)
  James Cagney, Don Murray
- 823. "Shanghai Express" (Box 10)
- 824. "She Done Him Wrong"1931 (Box 11)
  Mae West, Cary Grant
- 825. "She Wrote the Book"1946 (Box 11)
- 826. "Shenandoah" (Box 11)
  James Stewart, Doug McClure, Glenn Corbett
- 827. "Sherlock Holmes and the Voice of Terror"1942 (Box 11)
  Basil Rathbone, Nigel Bruce, Thomas Gomez, Evelyn Ankers
- 828. "Ship of Fools" (Box 11)
  Vivien Leigh, Simone Signoret, Jose Ferrer, Lee Marvin
- 829. "Shoot the Chutes"1935, 4 (Box 11)
- 830. "A Shot in the Dark" (Box 11)
  Peter Sellers, Elke Sommer
- 831. "Shoulder Arms" (Box 11)
- 832. "Show Boat" (Box 11)
  Howard Keel, Kathryn Grayson, Ava Gardner
- 833. "Show Business" 1944, 7 (Box 11)
- 834. "Show People"1928 (Box 11)
  Charlie Chaplin, Marion Davies, Bill Haines
- 835. "Siegfried", 21 (Box 11)
  U.F.A picture
- 836. "Silken Skin" (Box 11)
  Jean Desailly, Francoise Dorleac, Nelly Benedetti
- 837. "The Silver Fleet" (Box 11)
  Ralph Richardson, Googie Withers
- 838. "The Silver King"1919 (Box 11)
  William Faversham
- 839. "Sin Town"1942 (Box 11)
  Anne Gwynne, Patric Knowles
- 840. "Sing, Baby, Sing", 2 (Box 11)
  Alice Faye, Adolphe Menjou
- 841. "Singapore"1947, 9 (Box 11)
  Fred MacMurray, Thomas Gomez
- 842. "The Singer Not The Song" (Box 11)
  Mylene Demongeot, John Mills
- 843. "Singer of Seville"1930, 2 (Box 11)
  Ramon Navarro, Dorothy Jordan
- 844. "Singing Kid"1936 (Box 11)
  Al Jolson
- 845. "The Sisters" (Box 11)
  Bette Davis, Errol Flynn
- 846. "Six Black Horses" (Box 11)
  Audie Murphy, Dan Duryea, Joan
- 847. "Six Bridges to Cross" (Box 11)
  Tony Curtis, Julie Adams, George Nader
- 848. "Skimpy" (Box 11)
  Hal Monty, Max Bygraves
- 849. "Sky West and Crooked" (Box 11)
  Hayley Mills, Ian McShane
- 850. "Slightly Scarlet"1955, 3 (Box 11)
  John Payne, Arlene Dahl
- 851. "Slim Carter" (Box 11)
  Jock Mahoney, Julie Adams
- 852. "Smart Woman" (Box 11)
- 853. "Smiley" (Box 11)
  Ralph Richardson, John McCallum, Chips Rafferty
- 854. "Smiley Gets A Gun" (Box 11)
  Chips Rafferty, Sybil Thorndike
- 855. "Soak The Rich" (Box 11)
  Ben Hecht, Charles MacArthur
- 856. "Sodom and Gomorrah" (Box 11)
  Stewart Granger, Stanley Baker, Pier
- 857. "Some Like It Hot" (Box 11)
  Marilyn Monroe, Jack Lemmon, Tony Curtis
- 858. "A Son Comes Home"1936 (Box 11)
  Mary Boland, Donald Woods, Roger Imhoff
- 859. "Son of Flubber" (Box 11)
  Fred MacMurray, Nancy Olson, Keenan Wynn
- 860. "Song of Scheherazade"1947 (Box 11)
  Eve Arden
- 861. "The Song of Songs" (Box 11)
- 862. "Song of the South" (Box 11)
  James Baskett, Bobby Driscoll
- 863. "Sons and Lovers" (Box 11)
  Wendy Hiller, Trevor Howard
- 864. "Sooky" (Box 11)
  Robert Coogan, Jackie Cooper
- 865. "Souls At Sea"1941 (Box 11)
  Robert Cummings, Jean Arthur
- 866. "South Pacific" (Box 11)
  Mitzi Gaynor, Rossano Brazzi, John Kerr
- 867. "The Speed Reporter", 2 (Box 11)
- 868. "The Spieler" (Box 11)
  Fred Kohler, Rene Adoree
- 869. "Sport of Kings"1942 (Box 11)
  Gordon Harker, Leslie Henson
- 870. "Sporting Love" (Box 11)
  Stanley Lupino, Laddie Cliff
- 871. "Spring Dance" (Box 11)
  Maureen O'Sullivan, Lew Ayres
- 872. "Spy Hunt"1950 (Box 11)
- 873. "The Spy Who Came In From The Cold" (Box 11)
- 874. "The Squawman"1931 (Box 11)
  Dustin Farnum, Winifred Kingston, Lupe Velez
- 875. "Stage Struck", 3 (Box 11)
  Dick Powell, Joan Blondell
- 876. "The Star Maker"1939 (Box 11)
  Bing Crosby, Louise Campbell
- 877. "State Secret", 3 (Box 11)
  Douglas Fairbanks, Jr., Glynis Johns
- 878. "Stay Away, Joe" (Box 11)
  Elvis Presley, Thomas Gomez, Joan
- 879. "Steamboat Round The Bend"1935, 2 (Box 11)
  Will Rogers
- 880. "Steel Key" (Box 11)
  Terence Morgan, Joan Rice
- 881. "Step Lively"1944 (Box 11)
  Anne Jeffreys
- 882. "Stolen Life"1939 (Box 11)
  Elisabeth Bergner, Michael Redgrave
- 883. "Stop, Look, and Love", 3 (Box 11)
  Jean Rogers, William Frawley
- 884. "Stop the World" (Box 11)
  Tony Tanner
- 885. "The Storm" (1930Lupe Velez, Paul Cavanagh (Box 11)
  2
- 886. "The Story of Molly X" (Box 11)
  June Havoc, John Russell
- 887. "Stowaway in the Sky" (Box 11)
  Maurice Baquet, Andre Gille
- 888. "Strange Lady In Town", 4 (Box 11)
  Greer Garson, Dana Andrews
- 889. "Strange World"1952, 5 (Box 11)
  Alexander Carlos, Angelica Hauff
- 890. "Stranger in the House" (Box 11)
  Geraldine Chaplin, James Mason
- 891. "Street of Forgotten Men"1925 (Box 11)
  Mary Brian, Neil Hamilton
- 892. "Stronger Than Fear" (Box 11)
  Dana Andrews, Farley Granger
- 893. "Swell Guy"1946, 2 (Box 11)
  Sonny Tufts, Ann Blyth, Thomas Gomez
- 894. "Submarine Seahawk", 11 (Box 11)
  John Bentley, Brett Halsey
- 895. "Summer Magic" (Box 11)
  Hayley Mills, Burl Ives, Dorothy McGuire
- 896. "Sunrise at Campabello" (Box 11)
  Sara Taft, Anne Loos
- 897. "Sunset Boulevard"1950 (Box 11)
  William Holden, Glioria Swanson,
- 898. "Sunset Pass"1929 (Box 11)
  Jack Holt
- 899. "Surrender"1927 (Box 11)
  Mary Philbin, Otto Matiesen
- 900. "Suspended Alibi", 6 (Box 11)
  Patrick Holt, Honor Blackman
- 901. "Sutter's Gold"1936, 3 (Box 11)
  Binnie Barnes, Edward Arnold
- 902. "Sweethearts", 2 (Box 11)
- 903. "Swiss Family Robinson"1939 (Box 11)
  Joyce Compton
- 904. "Sylvestre Bonnard"1935 (Box 11)
  Anne Shirley
- 905. "Syncopation"1942, 4 (Box 11)
- 906. "A Tale of Two Cities" (Box 11)
  Dirk Bogarde, Dorothy Tutin
- 907. "Tall In The Saddle"1944 (Box 11)
  John Wayne
- 908. "Tamango" (Box 11)
  Dorothy Dandridge, Curt Jurgens
- 909. "The Taming of the Shrew"1967 (Box 11)
  Elizabeth Taylor, Richard
- 910. "Tarnished" (Box 11)
  Dorothy Patrick, Arthur Franz
- 911. "Tarzan"1954, 2 (Box 11)
  Gordon Scott
- 912. "Tarzan And The Valley Of Gold" (Box 11)
  Mike Henry
- 913. "Tarzan Goes To India" (Box 11)
  Jock Mahoney
- 914. "Tarzan's Hidden Jungle" (Box 12)
  Gordon Scott, Vera Miles
- 915. "Taste the Blood of Dracula" (Box 12)
- 916. "Tawny Pipit", 5 (Box 12)
  Bernard Miles, Rosamund John
- 917. "The Teacher", 2 (Box 12)
  L. Shabalina
- 918. "Teenage Millionaire" (Box 12)
  Jimmy Clanton, Rocky Graziano,
- 919. "Tembo" (Box 12)
  Howard Hill
- 920. "The Ten Commandments"1923 (Box 12)
- 921. "The Tenderfoot", 2 (Box 12)
  Brian Keith, Brandon de Wilde
- 922. "The Texan"1930 (Box 12)
- 923. "The Texans"1938 (Box 12)
  Joan Bennett, Randolph Scott
- 924. "The Texas Rangers"1936, 3 (Box 12)
  Fred MacMurray, Jean Parker
- 925. "That Darn Cat" (Box 12)
  Dean Jones, Hayley Mills
- 926. "That Funny Feeling" (Box 12)
  Donald O'Connor, Bobby Darin, Sandra
- 927. "That Man In Istanbul" (Box 12)
  Horst Buchholz, Sylva Koscina, Klaus Kinski
- 928. "That Riviera Touch" (Box 12)
  Eric Morecambe, Ernie Wise, Suzanne
- 929. "That's Right, You're Wrong"1939 (Box 12)
  Kay Kayser
- 930. "Their Own Desire"1930 (Box 12)
  Norma Shearer, Belle Bennett
- 931. "They're A Weird Mob", 2 (Box 12)
  Walter Chiari, Clare Dunne
- 932. "Thin Ice", 3 (Box 12)
  Alan Hale, Sonja Henie, Tyrone Power
- 933. "The Thing From Another World" (Box 12)
- 934. "This Earth Is Mine" (Box 12)
  Jean Simmons, Rock Hudson, Dorothy McGuire, Clade Rains
- 935. "This Gun For Hire" (Box 12)
- 936. "This Happy Feeling"1958 (Box 12)
  Curt Jurgens, Debbie Reynolds, John Saxon, Estelle Winwood
- 937. "This Is Heaven"1929 (Box 12)
  Vilma Banky
- 938. "This Is My Love" (Box 12)
  Linda Darnell, Dan Duryea
- 939. "This Is My Street", 31 (Box 12)
  Ian Hendry, June Ritchie
- 940. "Thoroughbreds Don't Cry", 2 (Box 12)
  Mickey Rooney, Judy Garland
- 941. "Thoroughly Modern Millie" (Box 12)
  Julie Andrews, James Fox,
- 942. "Those Kids From Town" (Box 12)
  Percy Marmont, Maire O'Neill
- 943. "Those Magnificent Men in Their Flying Machines" (Box 12)
  Sarah Miles, Stuart Whitman
- 944. "Three Brave Men" (Box 12)
  Ernest Borgnine, Virginia Christine
- 945. "Three Into Two Won't Go" (Box 12)
  Claire Bloom, Rod Steiger
- 946. "Three Live Ghosts"1929 (Box 12)
  Claud Allister, Charles McLaughton,
- 947. "Three Sisters" (Box 12)
  Alan Bates, Joan Plowright, Derek Jacobi
- 948. "The Thrill Of It All" (Box 12)
  James Garner, Doris Day
- 949. "Thunder"1929 (Box 12)
  Lon Chaney, Phyllis Haver
- 950. "Thunder in the East" (Box 12)
  Alan Ladd, Deborah Kerr
- 951. "Thunderball"1965, 2 (Box 12)
  Sean Connery
- 952. "Thunderbird", 5 (Box 12)
- 953. "Thunderbolt" (Box 12)
- 954. "Tiari Tahiti"1962 (Box 12)
  James Mason, John Mills
- 955. "The Tide of Empire" (Box 12)
  Renee Adoree, George Fawcett
- 956. "Tiger Bay" (Box 12)
  John Mills, Horst Buchholz, Hayley Mills
- 957. "Tiger in the Smoke" (Box 12)
- 958. "The Tiger Man" (Box 12)
  Richard Arlen, Vera Ralston, Erich Von
- 959. "Tillie's Punctured Romance" (Box 12)
  Mack Swain, Louise Fazenda
- 960. "Tillie's Tomato Surprise" (Box 12)
  Marie Dressler
- 961. "Time Gentlemen Please", 2 (Box 12)
  Eddie Byrne, Raymond Lovell
- 962. "A Time To Live And A Time To Die" (Box 12)
  Maurice Ronet, Jeanne Moreau
- 963. "To Kill A Mockingbird"1963, 5 (Box 12)
- 964. "Tobruk", 6 (Box 12)
  Rock Hudson, George Peppard
- 965. "The Toilers"1928 (Box 12)
  Douglas Fairbanks, Jr., Jobyna Ralston
- 966. "Tokyo After Dark" (Box 12)
- 967. "Tom Sawyer" (Box 12)
  Toomy Kelly, Jackie Moran
- 968. "Tomboy and the Champ" (Box 12)
  Candy Moore, Ben Johnson
- 969. "Tommy the Toreador" (Box 12)
  Tommy Steele, Janet Munro
- 970. "Tons of Money"1942 (Box 12)
  Ralph Lynn, Yvonne Arnaud
- 971. "Torchy Comes Through", 2 (Box 12)
  Johnny Hines, Billie Dove
- 972. "The Totem Mark"1911 (Box 12)
  Jack Conway, J. Barney Sherry
- 973. "Tough Guy" (Box 12)
- 974. "The Trail of the Lonesome Pine"1935 (Box 12)
  Sylvia Sidney, Fred
- 975. "The Train" (Box 12)
  Burt Lancaster, Paul Scofield
- 976. "Transatlantic Merry-Go-Round"1934 (Box 12)
  Gene Raymond, Nancy Carrol, Jack Benny
- 977. "Transgression"1931 (Box 12)
  Kay Francis, Ricardo Cortez
- 978. "The Trap" (Box 12)
  Rita Tushingham, Barbara Chilcott
- 979. "Treasure Island" (Box 12)
  Bobby Driscoll, Robert Newton
- 980. "The Trial of Mary Dugan" (Box 12)
  Norma Shearer, Lewis Stone
- 981. "Trifling Women" (Box 12)
  Lewis Stone, Barbara La Mar, Roman
- 982. "Tropic By Night", 3 (Box 12)
- 983. "Tropic Holiday"1938 (Box 12)
  Dorothy Lamour, Bob Burns, Martha
- 984. "The Trouble Shooter" (Box 12)
  Robert Mitchum, Jan Sterling
- 985. "True As A Turtle" (Box 12)
  John Gregson, June Thorburn
- 986. "True To The Navy"1930 (Box 12)
- 987. "Trust Your Wife"1921 (Box 12)
- 988. "Truth About Spring", 2 (Box 12)
  Hayley Mills, John Mills
- 989. "Tunes of Glory", 7 (Box 12)
  John Mills, Alec Guinness
- 990. "Turkey Time" (Box 12)
- 991. "Turmoil"1936 (Box 12)
  Don Ameche, Jean Hersholt
- 992. "12 Mile Reef"1953, 2 (Box 12)
  Gilbert Roland, Robert Wagner
- 993. "Twilight For The Gods" (Box 12)
  Rock Hudson, Cyd Charisse
- 994. "Two's Company" (Box 12)
  Ned Sparks, Mary Brian
- 995. "Two-Way Stretch", 3 (Box 12)
  Peter Sellers, Wilfrid Hyde White
- 996. "Two White Arms" (Box 12)
- 997. "Typhoon Bill" (Box 12)
- 998. "Tyrant of the Sea" (Box 12)
  Rhys William, Ron Randell
- 999. "The Ugly American" (Box 13)
  Marlon Brando, Sandra Church
- 1000. "The Ugly Dachshund"1965 (Box 13)
  Dean Jones, Suzanne Pleshette
- 1001. "Ulysses" (Box 13)
- 1002. "The Unchastened Woman" (Box 13)
  Theda Bara
- 1003. "Under the Pines"1911, 8 (Box 13)
  Viola Barry, Hobart Bosworth
- 1004. "Under Two Flags"1936 (Box 13)
  Claudette Colbert, Ronald Colman, John Carradine
- 1005. "Unexpected Father" (Box 13)
  Claude Allister, Slim Summerville,
- 1006. "Union Pacific"1939, 13 (Box 13)
- 1007. "Unknown World" (Box 13)
  Bruce Kellogg, Otto Waldis
- 1008. "Upstage"1926 (Box 13)
- 1009. "Ursus In The Land Of Fire" (Box 13)
  Ed Fury, Claudia Mori
- 1010. "The Valiant" (Box 13)
  John Mills, Ettore Manni, Roberto Risso
- 1011. "Valley of Fury" (Box 13)
  Victor Mature, Suzan Ball, John Lund
- 1012. "Valley of the Kings" (Box 13)
  Robert Taylor, Eleanor Parker
- 1013. "Valley of Song" (Box 13)
  Mervyn Johns, Clifford Evans
- 1014. "Vanity Fair" (Box 13)
  Mabel Ballin, Hobart Bosworth
- 1015. "Varsity"1928, 2 (Box 13)
  Buddy Rogers, Mary Brian
- 1016. "The Veils of Bagdad" (Box 13)
  Victor Mature, Mari Blanchard
- 1017. "Very Important Person" (Box 13)
  James Robertson Justice
- 1018. "The Victors" (Box 13)
  Eli Wallach, George Hamilton, George Peppard, Mames mitchum
- 1019. "La Vie De Chateau" (Box 13)
  Catherine Deneuve, Philippe Noiret
- 1020. "Village of the Damned" (Box 13)
  George Sanders, Barbara Shelley
- 1021. "The Villain Still Pursued Her"1940 (Box 13)
  Buster Keaton, Richard
- 1022. "Violent Playground", 4 (Box 13)
  Stanley Baker, Peter Cushing
- 1023. "Virgin Island", 2 (Box 13)
  John Cassavetes, Virginia Maskell
- 1024. "Virginia"1940 (Box 13)
- 1025. "Virginia City" (Box 13)
  Errol Flynn, Miriam Hopkins, Randolph
- 1026. "The Virginian"1929, one still from the (Box 13)
- 1027. "Viva Las Vegas" (Box 13)
  Dan Dailey, Cyd Charisse
- 1028. "Volcano", 2 (Box 13)
  Anna Magnani, Rossano Brazzi
- 1029. "Von Ryan's Express" (Box 13)
  Frank Sinatra, Trevor Howard
- 1030. "The Walking Dead"1936 (Box 13)
  Boris Karloff
- 1031. "Waltz King" (Box 13)
  Kerwin Mathews, Brian Aherne, Senta Berger
- 1032. "Wanderlust"1935 (Box 13)
  Guy Kibbee, Aline MacMahon
- 1033. "The War Is Over" (Box 13)
  Yves Montand, Ingrid Thulin
- 1034. "War of the Trojans" (Box 13)
  Steve Reeves
- 1035. "Way for a Pirate"1936 (Box 13)
  Guy Kibbee
- 1036. "The Way To Love"1933 (Box 13)
  Maurice Chevalier, Ann Dvorak
- 1037. "Weather or No"1937 (Box 13)
  Ralph Bellamy, Ida Lupino
- 1038. "The Web" (Box 13)
  Edmond O'Brien, Ella Raines
- 1039. "Wells Fargo"1937, 2 (Box 13)
  Joel McCrea, Frances Dee
- 1040. "West of Zanzibar" (Box 13)
  Lon Chaney
- 1041. "West Side Story", 3 (Box 13)
  Natalie Wood, Russ Tamblyn
- 1042. "What A Widow!", 2 (Box 13)
  Gloria Swanson, Owen Moore
- 1043. "What Men Want" (Box 13)
  Pauline Starke, Robert Ellis
- 1044. "What Price Beauty"1928 (Box 13)
- 1045. "What Price Glory" (Box 13)
- 1046. "What Women Give"1933 (Box 13)
  Lewis Stone, Phillip Holmes
- 1047. "When Love Is Young"1937 (Box 13)
  Walter Brennan, Virginia Bruce
- 1048. "Where Danger Lives" (Box 13)
  Faith Domergne
- 1049. "Where The Boys Are" (Box 13)
  Dolores Hart, George Hamilton
- 1050. "Where The Spies Are" (Box 13)
  David Niven, Francoise Dorleac
- 1051. "The Whisperers" (Box 13)
  Edith Evans, Eric Portman
- 1052. "White Fang"1936 (Box 13)
  Jean Muir, Michael Whalen
- 1053. "The White Rose", 2 (Box 13)
  Mae Marsh
- 1054. "White Savage"1943, 8 (Box 13)
  Thomas Gomez
- 1055. "The White Sister", 13 (Box 13)
  Lillian Gish, Ronald Colman
- 1056. "White Tie And Tails", 2 (Box 13)
  Dan Duryea, Ella Raines
- 1057. "The White Tower" (Box 13)
  Oscar Homolka
- 1058. "Who Done It"1942 (Box 13)
  Abbott and Costello, Mary Wickes, Louise
- 1059. "Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf?"1966 (Box 13)
  Sandy Dennis, George Segal
- 1060. "Why Change Your Wife"1920 (Box 13)
  Thomas Meighan, Kathleen Williams
- 1061. "The Wicked Go To Hell" (Box 13)
  Marina Vlady, Robert Hossein
- 1062. "Wife, Doctor, and Nurse"1937 (Box 13)
  Loretta Young, Warner Baxter, Virginia Bruce
- 1063. "Wife Vs. Secretary" (Box 13)
  Myrna Loy, Jean Harlow, Clark Gable
- 1064. "Wild Is The Wind" (Box 13)
  Anna Magnani, Anthony Quinn
- 1065. "William At The Circus", 2 (Box 13)
  Garry Marsh, Jane Welsh
- 1066. "Wilson", 3) (Box 13)
  Alexander Knox, Geraldine Fitzgerald
- 1067. "The Wind Cannot Read" (Box 13)
  Dirk Bogarde, Yoko Tani
- 1068. "Wings"1927 (Box 13)
- 1069. "Winter Carnival"1939, 6 (Box 13)
  Ann Sheridan, Richard Carlson
- 1070. "Within The Law" (Box 13)
- 1071. "Without Reservations" (Box 13)
  Claudette Colbert, John Wayne
- 1072. "Without Warning" (Box 13)
  Meg Randall, Edward Binns
- 1073. "Witness For The Prosecution" (Box 13)
  Tyrone Power, Marlene
- 1074. "The Wizard of Baghdad" (Box 13)
  Dick Shawn, Diane Baker
- 1075. "The Wizard of Oz"1939 (Box 13)
  Judy Garland, Ray Bolger, Jack Haley,
- 1076. "The Wolf Man" (Box 13)
- 1077. "Wolf of Wall Street"1929 (Box 13)
  Paul Lukas, George Bancroft
- 1078. "A Woman Destroyed"1946 (Box 13)
  Susan Hayward, Lee Bowman, Eddie Albert
- 1079. "Woman in a Dressing Gown" (Box 13)
  Yvonne Mitchell, Sylvia Syms, Anthony quayle
- 1080. "The Woman I Love"1937 (Box 13)
  Paul Muni, Miriam Hopkins
- 1081. "A Woman's Man"1934 (Box 13)
  Tommy Dugan, Wallace Ford
- 1082. "Woman Obsessed" (Box 13)
  Susan Hayward
- 1083. "Woman of Rome" (Box 13)
  Gina Lollobrigida, Daniel Gelin
- 1084. "Woman on Pier 13"1949 (Box 13)
- 1085. "A Woman's Privilege" (Box 13)
  Bernard Archard, Ann Lynn
- 1086. "Women In Love", 2 (Box 13)
  Glenda Jackson, Oliver Reed
- 1087. "Wonder of Women"1929 (Box 13)
  Lewis Stone, Peggy Wood
- 1088. "Wonderful World of the Brothers Grimm" (Box 13)
  Laurence Harvey, Claire Bloom, Karl Boehm
- 1089. "Work...Is A Four-Letter Word" (Box 13)
  David Warner
- 1090. "The World of Henry Orient" (Box 13)
  Peter Sellers, Paula Prentiss, Angela Lansbury
- 1091. "A Yank At Oxford" (Box 13)
  Robert Taylor, Lionel Barrymore,
- 1092. "Yankee Buccaneer" (Box 13)
  Jeff Chandler, Scott Brady
- 1093. "Yesterday's Enemy" (Box 13)
- 1094. "You Have To Run Fast" (Box 13)
  Craig Hill, Elaine Edwards
- 1095. "You Must Be Joking!" (Box 13)
  Michael Callan, Lionel Jeffries,
- 1096. "You Only Live Twice", 3 (Box 13)
- 1097. "Young Eagles"1930 (Box 13)
  Jean Arthur, Charles "Buddy" Rogers
- 1098. "The Young Girls of Rochefort" (Box 13)
  Gene Kelly, George
- 1099. "The Young Have No Time" (Box 13)
  Ghita Norby, Fris Helmuth
- 1100. "Your Money Or Your Wife" (Box 13)
  Donald Sinden, Peggy
- 1101. "You're A Sweetheart" (Box 13)
  Alice Faye, George Murphy
- 1102. "Zarak" (Box 13)
  Victor Mature, Anita Ekberg
- 1103. Unidentified film stills, 11 (Box 13)